Slocum mss., 1955-2012 LMC 2681
Lilly Library
- XIX. Miscellaneous Puzzle-related Materials (Box 83 (Oversize))
  - Puzzle Bible, 1995 (Box 93)
  - Nuts to Crack from Tim Turner, 2009 (Box 93)
  - Tonight Show materials, October 10, 1986 (Box 93)
  - Jeux exhibition catalog, 1992 (Box 93)
  - Articles, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 93)
  - Cartoons, undated (Box 93)
  - Publicity materials, undated (Box 93)
  - Biographical materials, undated (Box 93)
  - Newspaper The Brooklyn Daily Eagle, January 3, 1897 (Box 95 (Oversize))
  - Calendars (Box 95 (Oversize))
  - Broadsides (Box 95 (Oversize))
  - Print Academe Francaise (Box 109 (Oversize))
  - Color photocopy of Rand McNally & Co.'s New Railroad and County Map of the United States and Canada, Library of Congress, Division of Maps, G3701.P3 1876 R34 RR59 (Box 110)
- XX. Additions (Box 111)
  - Gathering4Gardner: Exchange Book, Vol I. (Box 111)
  - Gathering4Gardner: Exchange Book, Vol II. (Box 111)
  - Gathering4Gardner: Exchange Book, miscellaneous materials, (7 folders) (Box 111)
  - "Anamorphic Art," article (Box 111)
  - Catalogs (Box 111)
  - International Intellectual Puzzle Exhibition, writing with puzzles (Box 111)
  - Samples for reviews (Box 111)
  - Guidelines for International Puzzle Collectors' Parties (Box 111)
    (NOTE: No copying or digitizing the contents of this folder)
  - Miscellaneous, (3 folders) (Box 111)
  - Ap-Art: A Compendium of Puzzle Designs photocopy of book (Box 112)
  - "Atteuristic Approach to Solution of Checkerboard Puzzles," photocopy (Box 112)
  - Burr puzzle analysis and solutions (Box 112)
  - Coffin instruction sheets, 30,060-30,087 (Box 112)
  - Coffin instruction sheets, 30,088 (Box 112)
  - Coffin puzzles data (Box 112)
  - "Fascinating Puzzles," bulletin (Box 112)
  - "Games and Puzzles Magazine Index" (Box 112)
  - Hlavolamy photocopy of book (Box 112)
  - "The Hungarian Cube," screenplay (Box 112)
  - "Julebuffen," photocopy (Box 112)
  - Magic Squares puzzles (Box 112)
  - Notebooks (Box 112)
  - "Puzzle Books, Magazines and Catalogs in the Slocum Puzzle Collection Library" (Box 112)
  - Puzzle Graphics DG (Box 112)
  - "Puzzle Instructions and Ephemera," photocopy of book (Box 112)
  - Puzzle lists, (2 folders) (Box 112)
  - Puzzles, Mathematical, Scientific and Dexterous, photocopy (Box 112)
  - Re-Kreation... dissertation, (3 folders) (Box 112)
  - Re-Kreation... appendices, (2 folders) (Box 112)
  - Rubik's Cube newsletter (Box 112)
  - Slocum Puzzle Library index (Box 112)
  - "Traditional Craft Techniques of Kanagawa," photocopy (Box 112)
  - "What's New in Polyomino Puzzles and Their Design?" (Box 112)
  - Zomeworks, pamphlet (Box 112)
  - Chinese vessels, history, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, info on books (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, notebook (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, Norman Sandfield, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, Smithsonian (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, UCLA (Box 113)
  - Chinese vessels, miscellaneous, (5 folders) (Box 113)
  - Puzzle-knives, appraisal lists and images (Box 113)
  - Puzzle-knives, lists (Box 113)
  - Puzzle vessels, history, (2 folders) (Box 113)
  - Puzzle vessels, Slocum Collection (Box 113)
  - Puzzle vessels, appendix (Box 113)
  - Russian puzzle vessels (Box 113)
  - Trick-knives, articles (Box 113)
  - Trick-knives, catalogs, history (Box 113)
  - Trick-knives, Dick Hamilton (Box 113)
  - Trick-knives, Steve Deer, notes (Box 113)
  - Tangram, annotated bibliography and references, (2 folders) (Box 114)
  - Tangram, book correspondence, Jack Botermans (Box 114)
  - Tangram, book correspondence, Harold Raizer (Box 114)
  - Tangram, book correspondence, Dic Sonneveld (Box 114)
  - Tangram, "buy books" (Box 114)
  - Tangram, "The Chinese Puzzler" (Box 114)
  - Tangram notes, copy (Box 114)
  - Tangram, "The New and Fashionable Chinese Puzzle," printed copy (Box 114)
  - Tangram, OCLC Bibliography, (3 folders) (Box 114)
  - Tangram, orders (Box 114)
  - "Photos of Tangram," printed photos, 1998-1999 (Box 114)
  - "Photos of Tangram," printed photos, 2000 (Box 114)
  - "Photos of Tangram," printed photos, 2001 (Box 114)
  - Tangram Book binder copy, 2000 (Box 114)
  - Tangram Book bound copy, 2001 (Box 114)
  - Tangram Book proof, 2002 (Box 115)
  - Tangram Book color copy proof (Box 115)
  - Tangram Book corrected final proofs, (2 folders) (Box 115)
  - Tangram Book layout with corrections (Box 115)
  - Tangram Book index (Box 115)
  - "Solutions to the Tangram Book: Pages 1 to 100" (Box 115)
  - "Supplement to the Tangram Book: Notes and Solutions" (Box 115)
  - Cracker Jack collections (Box 115)
  - COSI, Ohio (Box 115)
  - Hoffman Puzzles (Box 115)
  - Karakuri (Box 115)
  - "Nob Yoshigahara: Remembrances By a Friend", 2004 (Box 115)
  - "Puzzles Old and New," labels, 2001 (Box 115)
  - Puzzle studies (Box 115)
  - Slocum Puzzles, PowerPoint printed slides, 2007 (Box 115)
  - Articles in tribute to Martin Gardner (Box 115)
  - Martin: Articles in Tribute to Martin Gardner bound, autographed copy (Box 115)
  - Supplement to Puzzleana, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Trick locks, Sotheby's Auction (Box 115)
  - Articles on algorithms (Box 116)
  - Articles on puzzles (Box 116)
  - Articles on Slocum and Slocum Collection (Box 116)
  - Articles on Tangrams (Box 116)
  - Catalogs and Solutions, (4 folders) (Box 116)
  - "Compendium of Mechanical Puzzles," from catalogs (Box 116)
  - Directory of Puzzle Collectors and Puzzle Sellers, master copy with corrections (Box 116)
  - Donation to the Slocum Puzzle Foundation (Box 116)
  - Paper Puzzles, solutions and articles, (2 folders) (Box 116)
  - Patents (Box 116)
  - Ptolemy's Top (Box 116)
  - Puzzle Exhibition, Children's Museum of Indianapolis, 1990 (Box 116)
  - Slocum Collection taxonomy (Box 116)
  - "Sunny-Side Up: The Children's Own Magazine", 1935 (Box 116)
  - "The Cube," Chinese edition, correspondence and research materials (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Cube solutions, Dieter Gebhardt (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Puzzle crazes, Rubik's Cube intro (Box 117)
  - Erno Rubik, introduction to book (Box 117)
  - Rubik's Cube, publicity and articles (Box 117)
  - Rubik's Cube, history (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Rubik's Cube, miscellaneous (2 folders) (Box 117)
  - Rubik's Cube book, copy of chapters (Box 117)
  - Rubik's Cube book, final draft (Box 117)
  - Cube puzzle book, copy (Box 117)
  - Solutions to all the Cube puzzles, final copy (Box 117)
  - Jaap's Puzzle Page, copy (Box 117)
  - NxNxN Cube, Dieter Gebhardt's solution (Box 117)
  - Jack Boterman, printed photos (Box 117)
  - Printed photos, Slocum Collection (Box 117)
  - Printed photos, Slocum Collection of Rotational Puzzles, Ephemera and Books (Box 117)
  - Rotational puzzles (Box 117)
  - Singmaster, history (Box 117)
  - Singmaster, miscellaneous (Box 117)
  - Geert Hellings, sections (Box 118)
  - "Geert's text" (Box 118)
  - "History of Rotational Cube Puzzles" (Box 118)
  - "History of Rubik's Cube," draft (Box 118)
  - "History of Rubik's Cube," 5th draft (Box 118)
  - Mongolian puzzles, (4 folders) (Box 118)
  - Rotational Cube Puzzles, solutions, (3 folders) (Box 118)
  - Rotational puzzles, hand-crafted (Box 118)
  - Rotational puzzles, copies (Box 118)
  - Rotational puzzles, miscellaneous (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Budapest (Mentes), 4-step solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Denny's solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Endl solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Harris solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Geert Hellings solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Hordern solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Huang/Gebhardt solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Jaap's solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Dan Knight's solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, Spiegel solution (Box 118)
  - Rubik's Cube, miscellaneous (Box 118)
  - Black Dog and Leventhal publishers (Box 119)
  - Cube book, reviews (Box 119)
  - Cube book, corrections (Box 119)
  - Cube book, acknowledgments, references, credits (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Top-10 list (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Hidetoshi Takeji (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Lee Tutt (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Adam Cowan (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Matt Shepit (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Andrew Cormier (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Anthony Greenhill (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Jean-Claude Constantin (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Aleh Hladzilin (Box 119)
  - Hand-Made Rotational Puzzle Makers: Katsuhiko Okamoto (Box 119)
  - Magic Domino (Box 119)
  - Meffert Catalog (Box 119)
  - Meffert Puzzles (Box 119)
  - Patents (Box 119)
  - Patents, Magic Polyhedra (Box 119)
  - Patents, rotational puzzles (Box 119)
  - Printed photos, Europe, 2008 (Box 119)
  - Printed photos, rotational puzzles (Box 119)
  - Puzzles ordered (Box 119)
  - Pyraminx solutions (Box 119)
  - Rotating combinatorial (Box 119)
  - Rotational puzzles, Jurgen Brandt (Box 119)
  - Rubik's Cube, bibliographies (Box 119)
  - Rubik's Cube, Larry Nichols lawsuit (Box 119)
  - Rubik's Cube, publicity and sales (Box 119)
  - Rubik's Cube, Slocum Collection (Box 119)
  - Rubik's Cube, miscellaneous (Box 119)
  - Rubik I, ads and articles, (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - "Skewbi," miscellaneous (Box 119)
  - Solution books (Box 119)
  - Speed-cubing (Box 119)
  - Twisty Mods, presentation (Box 119)
  - "Twisty" puzzles (Box 119)
  - Vadim Grishin collection (Box 119)
  - X's egg (Box 119)
  - Computer Horizon Corporation, 1989 Annual Report (Box 120)
  - The Cube, reviews, publicity, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Cube book, figures (Box 120)
  - Cube book, invoices (Box 120)
  - Cube book, solution diagrams (Box 120)
  - Cube book file, articles (Box 120)
  - Cube, Dan Knight, illustrations and moves (Box 120)
  - "Cubing Notation," by Dan Harris (Box 120)
  - International puzzles (Box 120)
  - Nichols Cube write-up (Box 120)
  - "Notes on the Magic Cube" (Box 120)
  - Petrovich, Russian puzzles (Box 120)
  - Photographs (Box 120)
  - Pocket Cube (Box 120)
  - "The Puzzles of Sam Cornwell" (Box 120)
  - Rotational Cube puzzles, solutions (Box 120)
  - Rubik's Cube Solution Project, solvers' forms (Box 120)
  - Rubik's Cube solutions (Box 120)
  - Rubik's Cube, miscellaneous (Box 120)
  - 2x2x2 Cube, solution (Box 120)
  - 4x4x4 Rubik's Revenge Cube (Box 120)
  - 5x5x5 Professor's Cube (Box 120)
  - V-Cube, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Singmaster Solution (Box 120)
  - Miscellaneous, (2 folders) (Box 120)
  - Correspondence (Box 121)
    - Bandelow, Christoph (Box 121)
    - Baptista, Augusto (Box 121)
    - Bopp, Nan and Bill (Box 121)
    - Cassidy, John (Box 121)
    - Cormier, Andrew (Box 121)
    - Donovan, Peter (Box 121)
    - Fisher, Tony (Box 121)
    - Foster, Thomas (Box 121)
    - Fox, Tyler (Box 121)
    - Gebhardt, Dieter (Box 121)
    - Haak, Hendrik (Box 121)
    - Hellings, Geert (Box 121)
    - Huang, Wei-Hwa (Box 121)
    - Kimura, Meiko (Box 121)
    - Konstantinos, Verdes (Box 121)
    - Larsen, Finn G. (Box 121)
    - Litwin, David (Box 121)
    - Morris, Jeff (Box 121)
    - Naval, Domingo (Box 121)
    - Osborne, John R. (Box 121)
    - Shortz, Will (Box 121)
    - Sieper, Susannah (Box 121)
    - Singmaster, David (Box 121)
    - Slocum, Jerry (Box 121)
    - Slocum, Tim (Box 121)
    - Sonneveld, Dic (Box 121)
    - Starr, Norton (Box 121)
    - Stegmann, Robert (Box 121)
    - Tutt, Lee (Box 121)
    - Uri, Dario (Box 121)
    - Wood, Trevor (Box 121)
    - Yewchuck, C.R. (Box 121)
    - Unidentified (Box 121)
  - Box of Collection and Museum photos (Box 121)
  - Box of Puzzle Books index cards (Box 121)
  - DVD Arthur Ganson presents a few Machines created between 1978 and 2004 (Box 122)
  - DVD, "Akio Kamei" (Box 122)
  - Videocassette, "The Weekly Special with Jerry Slocum" (Box 122)
  - Videocassette, "IPP-22: Dinner, Presentations and Show" (Box 122)
  - Videocassette, "Puzzle" (film) (Box 122)
  - Videocassette, "H. Raizer" (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Ron Resch Work (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Applied Computational Intelligence lab (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Ted, 2004 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Slocum in Australia (photos), 2007 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Photos of Slocum Collection (Rotational puzzles, ephemera and books), July 2008 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Wei-Hwa/Dieter Solutions, 2008 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Rotational Book Project, backup files, 2008 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Europe photos, 2008 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, Rotational cube puzzle photos sources (backup), 2008 (Box 122)
  - CD-ROM, still photos from G4G5 (Box 122)
  - CD (music), Diana Deutsch: Phantom Words and Other Curiosities (Box 122)
  - Miscellaneous photographs (2 sleeves) (Box 122)
  - Box of Slocum photos (books, TV) (Box 122)
  - Box of index cards (Box 122)
  - Anchor Puzzles and Solutions Masters (Box 123)
  - Richter Book, 1887 (Box 123)
  - Richter Catalog, 1909 (Box 123)
  - Catalogs, LeipzigDr. Oskar Schneider, 1915 (Box 123)
  - Richter Catalog, 1913 (Box 123)
  - Catalogs and Price Lists (duplicates), Anchor Puzzles (Box 123)
  - Anchor Puzzles, #1-#36, (36 folders) (Box 123)
  - Anchor, Pfeifenraucher (Box 123)
  - Anchor, Marchen Bilder (Box 123)
  - Zoologischer Garten (Box 123)
  - Stern Ratsel Star Puzzle (Box 123)
  - Piccolo (Box 123)
  - Anchor, Mosaik #1-#4, (4 folders) (Box 123)
  - Anchor, Lustige Tiere (Box 123)
  - Richter Building Sets (Box 123)
  - Richter Anchor, (2 binders) (Box 123)
  - Richter Anchor, (2 binders) (Box 124)
  - Have/WTD. Form (Box 124)
  - Extra, For Trade - Anchor (Box 124)
  - Have/WTD. - List (Box 124)
  - Wanted, Anchor (Box 124)
  - Have - Form, Anchor (Box 124)
  - Have - List, Anchor (Box 124)
  - Wanted, Anchor Puzzles (Box 124)
  - Languages (Box 124)
  - Multi-label Anchor Puzzles (Box 124)
  - The Nine (Alle Neune), 1899 (Box 124)
  - Lightning Conductor, 1893 (Box 124)
  - Columbus Egg (El Des Columbus), 1893 (Box 124)
  - Patience Prover, 1896 (Box 124)
  - Trouble Killer (Grillen Toter), 1893 (Box 124)
  - Heart (Hertz Ratsel), 1907 (Box 124)
  - Goblin (Kobold), 1899 (Box 124)
  - Anchor Puzzle Production Data (Box 124)
  - Tangram (Box 124)
  - Anchor Puzzle Ads (Kopfzerbrecher), 1890 (Box 124)
  - Georgens vs. Anchor (Box 124)
  - Richter Tangrams (Box 124)
  - Circular (Kreisratsel), 1891 (Box 124)
  - Cross, 1892 (Box 124)
  - Not Too Hasty (Nicht Zu Hitzig), 1894 (Box 124)
  - Pythagoras, 1891 (Box 124)
  - Tormentor, 1891 (Box 124)
  - Be Quiet (Ruhig Blut), 1899 (Box 124)
  - Sphinx, 1899 (Box 124)
  - Magic Egg, 1912 (Box 124)
  - Wrath Breaker (Zornbrecher), 1893 (Box 124)
  - Star (Stern Ratsel), 1892 (Box 124)
  - Richter's Social Game, 1896 (Box 124)
  - 18-36-Booklets (Box 124)
  - Solution Books (Box 124)
  - Solution Books Data File (Box 124)
  - Solution, Gratis, 2nd Books (Box 124)
  - Anker, Strange Numbers, English (Box 124)
  - Anker - Wooden (Box 124)
  - Hippocratic Temperaments (Box 124)
  - Tafelchenlegen Mosaic Toy (Box 124)
  - Funny Animals and Fairy Tale Pictures, Mar. 1917 (Box 124)
  - Max and Mortiz, 1922 (Box 124)
  - Picco/Pikko (Box 124)
  - Piccolo, 1913 (Box 124)
  - Blumenspiel Flower, 1922 (Box 124)
  - Wizard (Box 124)
  - Puzzle Drive Puzzles (Box 124)
  - Question Puzzles (Box 124)
  - Barbarossa (Box 124)
  - Red Beard (Box 124)
  - Swedish Anchor Puzzles (Box 125)
  - White Beard (Box 125)
  - 1-17 Puzzle (and Star) Series (Box 125)
  - 18-36 Puzzle Series (Box 125)
  - Plastic Box Puzzles (Box 125)
  - Anchor Cross Copies (Box 125)
  - Yellow-Black Cross Puzzle, 1916 (Box 125)
  - Mosaik Puzzles, 1917 (Box 125)
  - Anchor Puzzle History, (binder) (Box 125)
  - Anchor Puzzle Chronology, 22 Jun. 2005 (Box 125)
  - Gebhardt History Write-ups (Box 125)
  - Start and Stop Dates, Puzzles (Box 125)
  - Dates/Chronology Richter (Box 125)
  - Dates from Puzzles (Box 125)
  - References - Puzzle Dates (Box 125)
  - Anker Series Dates Summary (Box 125)
  - Dates, Last (Box 125)
  - Extra Copies, Dates, Reference Material (Box 125)
  - Timelines, Anchor Puzzles (Box 125)
  - Richter's Competitors, Draft and Info (Box 125)
  - Art History, Text and Future Sections (Box 125)
  - Design, Manuf. Richter Art, Draft (Box 125)
  - Photos, Ulrike in Villa (Box 125)
  - Bibliographies, Richter/Anicer (Box 125)
  - Printer's Marksvs., 1900; 1919 (Box 125)
  - New Printer's Marks (Box 125)
  - Printer's Marks, Countries, Languages (Box 125)
  - Printer's Marks, Summary (Box 125)
  - Printer's Marks, Books and Boxes (Box 125)
  - MLB, Printer's Marks (Box 125)
  - Early Anker Series I, 1932 (Box 125)
  - Original Richter Series I, Sets (Box 125)
  - Anker Series I, Late 1953 (Box 125)
  - Georgeus - Richter (Box 125)
  - Richter Group Ads, Several Puzzles (Box 125)
  - Gratis Books (Box 125)
  - Second Books (Box 125)
  - Austria Ads (Box 125)
  - California Ads (Box 125)
  - Czech Ads (Box 125)
  - Croatian Ads (Box 125)
  - Dutch Daily Puzzles (Box 125)
  - Hungarian Ads (Box 125)
  - Italian Ads (Box 125)
  - Slovenia Ads (Box 125)
  - Art Styles, (until) 1910 (Box 125)
  - Pfeifen Raucher (Box 125)
  - Family Puzzles Series 1 and 2 (Box 125)
  - Original Richter (Box 125)
  - Original Richter, Richter Karam (Box 125)
  - Original Richter Puzzles and Blocks (Box 125)
  - Original Richter (Box 125)
  - Richter Artists (Box 125)
  - Book Sellers and Books to Buy (Box 125)
  - Meyer Heim, Paul (Box 125)
  - Richter Artist, Paul Meyerheim (Box 125)
  - Jungnickel, Ludwig H., Artist, Red Beard? (Box 126)
  - Burger, Ludwig (Box 126)
  - Olfers Books (Box 126)
  - Rohling, Carl (Box 126)
  - Puzzle Stones (Box 126)
  - Richter Testimonials (Box 126)
  - Numbering Puzzles (Box 126)
  - Richter Auctions (Box 126)
  - Anker Auction (Box 126)
  - MLB, Austria (Box 126)
  - Vienna Factory (Box 126)
  - Russian Richter History (Box 126)
  - Russian Anchor Puzzles (Box 126)
  - MLB, New Factory (Box 126)
  - (Anker), 2001-2005 (Box 126)
  - Richter, 1994-2005 (Box 126)
  - Modern Anker Puzzles (Box 126)
  - Anker #1 and #3, 1913 (Box 126)
  - Anker Factories, Illustrations (Box 126)
  - Swiss, Trench, German (Box 126)
  - Trench Puzzle (Box 126)
  - Zoo, Schutzengraben, 1914 (Box 126)
  - Hippocrates, 4 Humors Mosaic Puzzle (continued) (Box 126)
  - MLB, Sales and Workers (Box 126)
  - Anchor Book, To Do, New Sections (Box 126)
  - Richter Photos (Box 126)
  - Anchor Box and Book Cover Designs (Box 126)
  - Reference Material, History (Box 126)
  - Anchor, Reference Data (Box 126)
  - Anchor Puzzle Book (Box 126)
  - Richter Dates with Correspondence (Box 126)
  - Branch Offices, Richter (Box 126)
  - Fricke, Albert Paul (Box 126)
  - Anker Puzzles (Box 126)
  - Union, A. Paul Articles (Box 126)
  - MLB, New York (Made Stones) (Box 126)
  - New York, Anchor Puzzles, Addresses, Catalogs (Box 126)
  - Anchor Puzzles, Ads, Catalogs (Box 126)
  - MLB, Ads, Logos, Cartoons, Catalogs (Box 126)
  - Anchor Ads, Richter, Germany (Box 126)
  - Anchor, Playthings and Trade Magazines (Box 126)
  - USA, Puzzle Ads (Box 126)
  - Additions, Ads (Box 126)
  - Ads, Hungary, Anchor Puzzles (Box 126)
  - Czech Anchor Ads (Box 126)
  - Innsbruder Nachrichen (Box 126)
  - Coburger Zeitung (Box 126)
  - Wiener Zeitung (Box 126)
  - Ads, Frankischer Kurier, Nurnberg (Box 126)
  - Freiburger Zeitung, Germany (Box 126)
  - Blocks, No Puzzles, 1890 (Box 126)
  - Ad Summary (Box 126)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung, Leipzig, 1843-1944 (Box 126)
  - Austria, Illustrirte Zeitung (Box 126)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1891 (Box 126)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1892 (Box 126)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1893 (Box 126)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1894 (Box 126)
  - Ads, Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1895 (Box 126)
  - Ads, Illustrirte Zeitung Puzzles, 1896 (Box 126)
  - Ads, Illustrirte Zeitung, 1897 (Box 127)
  - Illustrirte Zeitung, 1901 (Box 127)
  - Illustrirte Fraven Zeitung (Box 127)
  - Ads, Library, Boston, Harvard (Box 127)
  - Austria Illustrirte Zeitung (Box 127)
  - Ad, Translations (Box 127)
  - Ads for 1-17, Richter Flyers and Catalogs (Box 127)
  - Richter Ads, 1st 4 Anchor Puzzles (Box 127)
  - Anchor Puzzle Ads (Box 127)
  - Dic's Lists, Anchor and Frichte (Box 127)
  - Translations, Anker Articles and Text (Box 127)
  - 50 Years, Richter in Rudolstadt, 1928 (Box 127)
  - Austria Newspapers (Box 127)
  - German/Austrian Magazines (Box 127)
  - SOYR, 1919 (Box 127)
  - Richter Magazine Clips (Box 127)
  - History, Misc., R.A.V., 1922 (Box 127)
  - Richter History. O. Hahn (Box 127)
  - Puzzle History, by C.J. Wijpooge, 1981 (Box 127)
  - Richter Family (Box 127)
  - MLB, Richter Family History (Box 127)
  - AHN, Inventory of Dr. Richter, 1911 (Box 127)
  - Anker History, by Jan Harver, 1989 (Box 127)
  - Rudolstadt Newspapers (Box 127)
  - Zwignenberg, Anchor History (Box 127)
  - Hardy, George (Box 127)
  - Article, 1989 (Box 127)
  - Article, 1986 (Box 127)
  - Employment, Richter (Box 127)
  - Frobel Kindergarten (Box 127)
  - Frobel Museum Puzzles (Box 127)
  - Georgens Books (Box 127)
  - Georgens, Tangram (Box 127)
  - MLB, Georgens /OLFERS (Box 127)
  - AHN, History/Frobel (Box 127)
  - AHN, Build Set List (Box 127)
  - Anchor, Meteor (Box 127)
  - Mah-Jong, 1919 (Box 127)
  - MLB, Heinzelmannchen (Box 127)
  - Modern Anchor Ads, Fliers, Booklets, etc., 1995 (Box 127)
  - Rudolstadt (Box 127)
  - AHN, Museum, Anker (Box 127)
  - MLB, Museums (Box 127)
  - Anker, Museum (Box 127)
  - Staatliche Museum, Berlin (Box 127)
  - Deutsches Spielzeng Museum, Sonneberg Puzzles (Box 127)
  - MLB, Exhibits at Rudolstadt (Box 127)
  - Patent Medicines (Box 127)
  - MLB, Pain Expeller (Box 127)
  - Richter's Patent Medicine Business in Holland (Box 127)
  - Peter Zwijenberg, Anchor Stones (Box 127)
  - Zwijenberg, Peter (Box 127)
  - Ads, Anchor Blocks (Box 127)
  - Richter USA, No Puzzles (Box 127)
  - Peter Zwijenberg's New Anchor History Book, Master Copy, 2007 (Box 127)
  - Book 1 - Puzzle Related Information: Mededelingenblad, Club van Ankervrienden (Box 127)
  - Book 2 - Puzzle Related Information: Mededelingenblad, Club van Ankervrienden (Box 127)
  - Mededelingenblad, Club van Ankervrienden, Jaargang 26, nr. 4, 2005 (Box 127)
  - Puzzle-Related Information: Anker Huis Nieuws (AHN), Dec. 1988 - Sept. 1996 (Box 127)
  - Anker Convention, 2005 (Box 128)
  - MLB, Magazine Index (Box 128)
  - CVA, CD Index (Box 128)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzle, Reference Catalogs, Flyers and Price Lists (Box 128)
  - Club Anker, Magazine with Puzzles (Box 128)
  - Richter's Anchor Magazine with Puzzles (Box 128)
  - Anker, Huiz, Paz Magazine with Puzzles (Box 128)
  - Anker, Zeitung (Box 128)
  - MLB - People, Collections, Richter (Box 128)
  - Anker-Zeitung, No. 13, 1926 (Box 128)
  - Anker-Zeitung, No. 1, 1913 (Box 128)
  - MLB, People, Collections, Richter (Box 128)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzle, Reference Catalogs, Flyers and Price Lists (Vol. 1 and 2) (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt correspondence, 2011 (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt correspondence, 2010 (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt correspondence, 2009 (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt drafts (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt, write, 1911-On (Box 128)
  - D.G., 1911-2007 (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt, 10/2007 (Box 128)
  - Gebhardt Reference Material (Box 128)
  - G. Hardy References, 6/27/04 (Box 128)
  - Hardy, Geo, Puzzles History (Box 128)
  - Hardy, George, Photos, 6/04 (Box 128)
  - Hardy, George Visit, 6/2004 (Box 128)
  - Geo. Hardy (Box 128)
  - Hardy Problems, AHN, 1992 (Box 128)
  - Hardy, George (Box 128)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzle... from the Collection of George Hardy (Box 128)
  - Dorothee Kummer (Box 128)
  - Max Kurtze Correspondence (Box 128)
  - Richter's Anchor Puzzles, Jerry Slocum's Correspondence with Dr. Max Kurtze (Box 128)
  - Max Kurtze Drafts (Box 128)
  - Raizer Correspondence (Box 129)
  - E. Meyer-Margeth, History of Stone Construction Sets (Box 129)